Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 22 (Box 1550)
    - Caption: Pan American plane at F.F. [France Field], 37
    - Caption: Pan American plane at F.F. [France Field], 38
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 23 (Box 1550)
    - Caption: Pan American Plane at F.F. [France Field], 1
    - Caption: Pan American Plane at F.F .[France Field], 2
    - France Field, Dargue [Caption: San Antonio damaged at France Field], 3
    - Verso: France Field, Dargue, 3-verso
    - [Caption: "San Antonio"damaged at France Field], 4
    - [Caption: Pan American Flight] Two pilots standing in front of their plane], 5
    - [Caption: Pan American Flight] Two pilots standing in front of their plane labled "Detroit"], 6
    - San Antonio; Caption: (Pan-American Flight), 7
    - Verso: San Antonio, 7-verso
    - Caption: View of Beach from Bluff, facing north. Alright here. Come ashore here; Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 8
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 8-verso
    - Caption: View of shore line, facing south. Beach; Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 9
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 9-verso
    - Asuncion, 10
    - Verso: Asuncion, 10-verso
    - Asuncion, 11
    - Verso: Asuncion, 11-verso
    - Caption: PUERTO DE SANTA FE - View to northeast, showing derivation channel and high susp. bridge. Suspension bridge, 12
    - Caption: Pure Sand Beach at Puerto Italia, 13
  Box 1551
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 1 (Box 1551)
    - Caption: Puerto Italia, facing east. Beach here, 1
    - Caption: Puerto de Santa Fe - Steel tower east of point of landing, often difficult to see hance especially dangerous., 2
    - Caption: Rocky, Firm sod, Rocky, 3
    - Arequipa, 4
    - Verso: Arequipa, 4-verso
    - Benton + Dargue before taking off from Manaqua, Nicaraqua January, 1928. Return to Mrs. Benton, 5
    - Verso: Benton + Dargue before taking off from Manaqua, Nicaraqua January, 1928. Return to Mrs. Benton, 5-verso
    - Dureau Field[?] Dargue; Caption: (Pan-American Flight), 6
    - Verso: Dureau Field[?] Dargue, 6-verso
    - Asuncion, 7
    - Verso: Asuncion, 7-verso
    - Asuncion, 8
    - Verso: Asuncion, 8-verso
    - Asuncion, 9
    - Verso: Asuncion, 9-verso
    - Asuncion, 10
    - Verso: Asuncion, 10-verso
    - Asuncion, 11
    - Verso: Asuncion, 11-verso
    - Asuncion, 12
    - Verso: Asuncion, 12-verso
    - Caption: Beach is below this bluff. Facing South, Port; Verso: Asuncion, 13
    - Verso: Asuncion, 13-verso
    - Puerto Belgrino [?], 14
    - Verso: Puerto Belgrino [?], 14-verso
    - Caption: Firm Sod, Park, Soft sandy mud in low water, 15
    - Buena ventura: Colombia, 16
    - Verso: Buena ventura: Colombia, 16-verso
    - Wilmington[?], 17
    - Verso: Wilmington[?], 17-verso
    - Guatemala City, 18
    - Verso: Guatemala City, 18-verso
    - The insigna painted on both sides of the body of each plane, 19
    - Verso: The insigna painted on both sides of the body of each plane, 19-verso
    - Mejillones, Chile., 20
    - Verso: Mejillones, Chile., 20-verso
    - Gulf of Fonseca; Anapola, Honduras [?], 21
    - Verso: Gulf of Fonseca; Anapola, Honduras [?], 21-verso
    - [Caption: Taking to the water at Franoc Field for the flight south], 22
    - Bogota, Presidential reception, 23
    - Verso: Bogota, Presidential reception, 23-verso
    - [Caption: Getting ready for the take off at France Field C.Z. "Pan American Flight"], 24
    - [Caption: At France Field C.Z. out to position for start south], 25
    - [Caption: "Pan American Flight"Taking position for start south], 26
    - Rolling into the Fort de France Bay, Martinique, French West Indies, 27
    - Verso: Rolling into the Fort de France Bay, Martinique, French West Indies, 27-verso
    - Trinidad, 28
    - Verso: Trinidad, 28-verso
    - Major Daique[?] discusses matter with captain H. Dermonest, American Consul; Arrival of Pan American Fliers at Port of Spain March 28/27, 29
    - Verso: Major Daique[?] discusses matter with captain H. Dermonest, American Consul; Arrival of Pan American Fliers at Port of Spain March 28/27, 29-verso
    - Puerto Cabello; Caption: Aveadaores del Raid Panamericans, 30
    - Verso: Puerto Cabello, 30-verso
    - Punta-Arenas - Costa Rica. Park, 31
    - Verso: Punta-Arenas - Costa Rica. Park, 31-verso
    - Grass boat-balsa Titicaca, 32
    - Verso: Grass boat-balsa Titicaca, 32-verso
    - Arequipa, 33
    - Verso: Arequipa, 33-verso
    - Lima; McDaniel, 34
    - Verso: Lima; McDaniel, 34-verso
    - Notice the dejected attitudes of the mechanics and the watchful stalking of Harris. Robbie isn t worried a but - he's busy with a Peruvian flea - Lima, 35
    - Verso: Notice the dejected attitudes of the mechanics and the watchful stalking of Harris. Robbie isn t worried a but - he's busy with a Peruvian flea - Lima, 35-verso
    - Trip to Bolivia, 36
    - Verso: Trip to Bolivia, 36-verso
    - [Man standing on a plane during the Pan-American Flight], 37
    - Grass boat Titicaca, 38
    - Verso: Grass boat Titicaca, 38-verso
    - Trip to Bolivia, 39
    - Verso: Trip to Bolivia, 39-verso
    - Arequipa, 40
    - Verso: Arequipa, 40-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 2 (Box 1551)
    - [Two pilots in a plane labled "Major H.A. Dargue L.T. E.C. Whitehead" from the Pan-American Flight], 1
    - [Caption: Pan-American Flight; suitcase labled "Major H.A. Dargue New York], 2
    - Verso: Duncan Field [illegible] The suitcases we used + working, 2-verso
    - At Miller Field, 3
    - Verso: At Miller Field, 3-verso
    - Mr. Curtiss in flying boat with canoe attached - 1910., 4
    - Verso: Mr. Curtiss in flying boat with canoe attached - 1910., 4-verso
    - Lima, 5
    - Verso: Lima, 5-verso
    - Left to right - Dick-the boy interpreter; Robbie-; Col. O'Connor-; Harris-; Maj. Winton-Military Attache; Mac-; Cole- Rigging + Engine instructor at "Las Palmas"; Briggs-American Consul office. Lima McDaniel, 6
    - Verso: Left to right - Dick-the boy interpreter; Robbie-; Col. O'Connor-; Harris-; Maj. Winton-Military Attache; Mac-; Cole- Rigging + Engine instructor at "Las Palmas"; Briggs-American Consul office. Lima McDaniel, 6-verso
    - Puerto Belgrano, 7
    - Verso: Puerto Belgrano, 7-verso
    - Caption: Puerto de Santa Fe - View to northeast, showing point of landing, steel tower and smokestack to the east of the port. Steel tower, 8
    - Valpo, 9
    - Verso: Valpo, 9-verso
    - Valpo, 10
    - Verso: Valpo, 10-verso
    - Port au Prince, 11
    - Verso: Port au Prince, 11-verso
    - [Two pilots of the Pan-American Flight in their plane labled "Major H.A. Dargue L.T. E.C. Whitehead"], 12
    - Port au Prince, 13
    - Verso: Port au Prince, 13-verso
    - Fort de France, 14
    - Verso: Fort de France, 14-verso
    - Cayenne, 15
    - Verso: Cayenne, 15-verso
    - Cayenne, 16
    - Verso: Cayenne, 16-verso
    - Uruguan [?] Flying School ([illegible]), 17
    - Verso: Uruguan [?] Flying School ([illegible]), 17-verso
    - Military Aviation School Montevideo, 18
    - Verso: Military Aviation School Montevideo, 18-verso
    - C.O. Aviation Sch Montevideo, 19
    - Verso: C.O. Aviation Sch Montevideo, 19-verso
    - Commandant of Military Flying School, Uruguay, 20
    - Verso: Commandant of Military Flying School, Uruguay, 20-verso
    - Wilmington; Maj. Dargue, 21
    - Verso: Wilmington; Maj. Dargue, 21-verso
    - Aviation Sch - Montevideo, 22
    - Verso: Aviation Sch - Montevideo, 22-verso
    - Major Dargue refueling the plane ar Pt. Isabel, Texas, 23
    - Verso: Major Dargue refueling the plane ar Pt. Isabel, Texas, 23-verso
    - One of Pan-Am plane being refuelled at Point Isabel, Texas, 24
    - Verso: One of Pan-Am plane being refuelled at Point Isabel, Texas, 24-verso
    - Col. Davis, Mil. At. At Mex City. Gen. Amezcua, Chief of Mex Aviaion[?] + Maj. Dargue on most of hangar witnessing flying demonstration, 25
    - Verso: Col. Davis, Mil. At. At Mex City. Gen. Amezcua, Chief of Mex Aviaion[?] + Maj. Dargue on most of hangar witnessing flying demonstration, 25-verso
    - Mexico City Ambassador + Mrs. Sheffield + Staff, 26
    - Verso: Mexico City Ambassador + Mrs. Sheffield + Staff, 26-verso
    - [Bermeja Barranca]: refueling Pan-American Flight plane, 27
    - Verso: [Bermeija Barranca] refueling, 27-verso
    - Midnight dance at Esperanza, 28
    - Verso: Midnight dance at Esperanza, 28-verso
    - Esparaza en route to Bogota, 29
    - Verso: Esparaza en route to Bogota, 29-verso
    - Dinner at Esperanza en route to Bogota, 30
    - Verso: Dinner at Esperanza en route to Bogota, 30-verso
    - France Field Dagque; Caption: Amphibians taking off, 31
    - Verso: France Field Dargue, 31-verso
    - At Miller Field, 32
    - Verso: At Miller Field, 32-verso
    - Fort de France, 33
    - Verso: Fort de France, 33-verso
    - Cayenne, 34
    - Verso: Cayenne, 34-verso
    - Mejillones; Maj. Dargue, 35
    - Verso: Mejillones; Maj. Dargue, 35-verso
    - Valparaiso; Maj. Dargue, 36
    - Verso: Valparaiso; Maj. Dargue, 36-verso
    - Valdina, 37
    - Verso: Valdina, 37-verso
    - Valpo, 38
    - Verso: Valpo, 38-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 39
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 39-verso
    - [Caption: Pan-American Flight flagship "New York" over Gatun Lake, CZ.], 40
    - [Men standing on an airplane from the Pan-American Flight], 41
    - [Plane from the Pan-American Flight landing in the water at France Field] Caption: Pan American Plane at F.F. [France Field], 42
    - [Pan-American Flight plane in Bermeja Barranca], 43
    - Verso: [Bermeja Barranca], 43-verso
    - Asuncion, 44
    - Verso: Asuncion, 44-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight plane landing in water] Caption: Valparaiso, 45
    - [Pan-American Flight plane landing in the water] Caption: Valparaiso, 46
    - At Miller Field, 47
    - Verso: At Miller Field, 47-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 3 (Box 1551)
    - Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 1
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 1-verso
    - Asuncion, 2
    - Verso: Asuncion, 2-verso
    - Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 3
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 3-verso
    - Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 4
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 4-verso
    - Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 5
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 5-verso
    - Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 6
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 6-verso
    - Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 7
    - Verso: Asuncion, Maj. Dargue, 7-verso
    - Asuncion, 8
    - Verso: Asuncion, 8-verso
    - Valdivia, 9
    - Verso: Valdivia, 9-verso
    - Valdivia, 10
    - Verso: Valdivia, 10-verso
    - Cayenne, 11
    - Verso: Cayenne, 11-verso
    - Cayenne, 12
    - Verso: Cayenne, 12-verso
    - Cayenne, 13
    - Verso: Cayenne, 13-verso
    - The Very Pistol, 14
    - Verso: The Very Pistol, 14-verso
    - Fort de France - A Lard looking Cot[?], 15
    - Verso: Fort de France - A Lard looking Cot[?], 15-verso
    - "New York" flagship of Pan American Flight coming out of Fort de France Bay. French West Indies, 16
    - Verso: "New York" flagship of Pan American Flight coming out of Fort de France Bay. French West Indies, 16-verso
    - Pan American Flight planes parked on Martinique, French West Indies; Rum factory parking area, 17
    - Verso: Pan American Flight planes parked on Martinique, French West Indies; Rum factory parking area, 17-verso
    - 50 man power at Fort de France, Martinique, 18
    - Verso: 50 man power at Fort de France, Martinique, 18-verso
    - Fort de France, 19
    - Verso: Fort de France, 19-verso
    - One wheel stuck with a blow out at Fort de France, Martinique., 20
    - Verso: One wheel stuck with a blow out at Fort de France, Martinique., 20-verso
    - [Plane from the Pan-American Flight taking off in water], 21
    - Verso: Away we go from Fort de France, Martinique, 21-verso
    - Fort de France, 22
    - Verso: Fort de France, 22-verso
    - Fort de France. Looks better than it really was, Rum factory in left background, 23
    - Verso: Fort de France. Looks better than it really was, Rum factory in left background, 23-verso
    - Verso: Martinique, leaving, 24
    - Martinique, leaving, 24-verso
    - Much help in getting ashore - Martinique, 25
    - Verso: Much help in getting ashore - Martinique, 25-verso
    - Flags of the 21 Pan American nations on a balloon at Bolling Field the day the flight returned, 26
    - Verso: Flags of the 21 Pan American nations on a balloon at Bolling Field the day the flight returned, 26-verso
    - Wilmington, Maj. Dargue, 27
    - Verso: Wilmington, Maj. Dargue, 27-verso
    - Wilmington, Maj. Dargue, 28
    - Verso: Wilmington, Maj. Dargue, 28-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 29
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 29-verso
    - [Two pilots from the Pan-American Flight standing in front of their plane], 30
    - [Pan-American Flight planes taking off in the water], 31
    - [Pan-American Flight planes in the air], 32
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 33
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 33-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 34
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 34-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 35
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 35-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 36
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 36-verso
    - The amphibious airplane we took, 37
    - Verso: The amphibious airplane we took, 37-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 38
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 38-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 39
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 39-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 40
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 40-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton; Use along west coast S. Am, 41
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton; Use along west coast S. Am, 41-verso
    - Port au Prince, Dargue, Mayor presenting banquet, 42
    - Verso: Port au Prince, Dargue, Mayor presenting banquet, 42-verso
    - Port au Prince, Dargue, 43
    - Verso: Port au Prince, Dargue, 43-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 4 (Box 1551)
    - Pan American Flight, Arrival at Port of Spain Trinidad, B.W.I., Major Dargue + his mechanic whatches[sic] the "San Antonio" comig ashore, 1
    - Verso: Pan American Flight, Arrival at Port of Spain Trinidad, B.W.I., Major Dargue + his mechanic whatches[sic] the "San Antonio" comig ashore, 1-verso
    - Cayenne, 2
    - Verso: Cayenne, 2-verso
    - Cayenne, 3
    - Verso: Cayenne, 3-verso
    - Cayenne, 4
    - Verso: Cayenne, 4-verso
    - Cayenne, 5
    - Verso: Cayenne, 5-verso
    - Cayenne, 6
    - Verso: Cayenne, 6-verso
    - Barranquilla Arrow indicates general direction of landings; copyright, Strictly confidential, 7
    - Verso: Barranquilla Arrow indicates general direction of landings; copyright, Strictly confidential, 7-verso
    - Girardot, 8
    - Verso: Girardot, 8-verso
    - [People standing in front of a plane, taken during the Pan-American Flight], 9
    - Girardot, Maj. Dargue, 9-verso
    - Scodta[?] people at Girardat, Dr. von [illegible] in center, 10
    - Verso: Scodta[?] people at Girardat, Dr. von [illegible] in center, 10-verso
    - Arrival Bogota, Maj. Darque, 11
    - Verso: Arrival Bogota, Maj. Darque, 11-verso
    - Girardot; copyright, Strictly confidential, 12
    - Verso: Girardot; copyright, Strictly confidential, 12-verso
    - Girardot, Arrow indicates general direction of landings. Dargue; copyright, Strictly confidential, 13
    - Verso: Girardot, Arrow indicates general direction of landings. Dargue; copyright, Strictly confidential, 13-verso
    - [Caption: San Antonio damaged at France Field.], 14
    - [Pan-American Flight plane nose-dived in water], 15
    - [People trying to get the Pan-American Flight plane out of the water], 16
    - [People gathered around a Pan-American Flight plane], 17
    - Amapala, Honduras Jan. 13, 1927, The beach was too soft to put our wheels down and run up in it as we did as little wading and swimming. We let the tide do out and leave the planes high + dry for refueling. Dargue, 18
    - Verso: Amapala, Honduras Jan. 13, 1927, The beach was too soft to put our wheels down and run up in it as we did as little wading and swimming. We let the tide do out and leave the planes high + dry for refueling. Dargue, 18-verso
    - [Portrait of an officer involved in the Pan-American Flight], 19
    - San Antonio Ready for take off, 20
    - Verso: San Antonio Ready for take off, 20-verso
    - Commanding General 8th Corps [illegible] S.A. + Maj. D. [Dargue], 21
    - Verso: Commanding General 8th Corps [illegible] S.A. + Maj. D. [Dargue], 21-verso
    - C.G. 8th C.A. + Maj. D. looking at map of route, 22
    - Verso: C.G. 8th C.A. + Maj. D. looking at map of route, 22-verso
    - Com. Gen. 8th C.A. + Maj. D. at S.A. with map of route, 23
    - Verso: Com. Gen. 8th C.A. + Maj. D. at S.A. with map of route, 23-verso
    - Grover Loening with Dargue + Whitehead, 24
    - Verso: Grover Loening with Dargue + Whitehead, 24-verso
    - On boat in floating gardens; [illegible], Mex., 25
    - Verso: On boat in floating gardens; [illegible], Mex., 25-verso
    - Mrs. Sheffield [illegible] a photo, Mex City, 26
    - Verso: Mrs. Sheffield [illegible] a photo, Mex City, 26-verso
    - Vera Cruz, Dinner at sidewalk caf, 27
    - Verso: Vera Cruz, Dinner at sidewalk caf, 27-verso
    - Lima, McDaniel, President Leguia at flying field, 28
    - Verso: Lima, McDaniel, President Leguia at flying field, 28-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton; City of La Paz and [illegible] grande vulcan Bolivia, 29
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton; City of La Paz and [illegible] grande vulcan Bolivia, 29-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 30
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 30-verso
    - The Major's Crash at Guatemala; Return to Mrs. Benton, 31
    - Verso: The Major's Crash at Guatemala; Return to Mrs. Benton, 31-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton; Alpacas, 32
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton; Alpacas, 32-verso
    - [Caption: Valparaiso; Pan-American Flight plane in water], 33
    - [People gathered around Pan-American Flight planes in the sand], 34
    - Valparaiso, Maj. Dargue, 35
    - Verso: Valparaiso, Maj. Dargue, 35-verso
    - Valparaiso, Maj. Dargue, 36
    - Verso: Valparaiso, Maj. Dargue, 36-verso
    - [People gathered around Pan-American Flight planes in the sand], 37
    - Valpo, 38
    - Verso: Valpo, 38-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton; Llammas and Misti vulcan Arequipa, 39
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton; Llammas and Misti vulcan Arequipa, 39-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton, 40
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 40-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton; City of Tiaguanaco [Tiahuanaco] Bolivia, 41
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton; City of Tiaguanaco [Tiahuanaco] Bolivia, 41-verso
    - Lake Titicaca Puno; Return to Mrs. Benton, 42
    - Verso: Lake Titicaca Puno; Return to Mrs. Benton, 42-verso
    - Mejillones, Maj. Dargue, 43
    - Verso: Mejillones, Maj. Dargue, 43-verso
    - Arequipa, 44
    - Verso: Arequipa, 44-verso
    - Trip to Bolivia, 45
    - Verso: Trip to Bolivia, 45-verso
    - Return to Mrs. Benton; Inca throne, Cuzco, 46
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton; Inca throne, Cuzco, 46-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 5 (Box 1551)
    - The wheels sunk in the mud at Port of Spain when coming ashore, 1
    - Verso: The wheels sunk in the mud at Port of Spain when coming ashore, 1-verso
    - Kingston, St. Vincent, B.W.I., 2
    - Verso: Kingston, St. Vincent, B.W.I., 2-verso
    - Refueling on the Magdakera R at Bamarca Berminja, Col. [?], 3
    - Verso: Refueling on the Magdakera R at Bamarca Berminja, Col. [?], 3-verso
    - On the Magdakera R at Bamarca Berminja, Col. [?], 4
    - Verso: On the Magdakera R at Bamarca Berminja, Col. [?], 4-verso
    - In the mire at Girardot, 5
    - Verso: In the mire at Girardot, 5-verso
    - [Caption: "Detroit" "San Francisco" "St. Louis". Off Porto Bello R.P. en route France Field to Columbia], 6
    - Sand Beach near Brito, Nicaragua Only emergency landing Field, 7
    - Verso: Sand Beach near Brito, Nicaragua Only emergency landing Field, 7-verso
    - Caption: First Flight-Pan American Ship, Oct 26 1926, Capt Woolsey - Pilot, Mr Grover Loening - Passenger; Verso: Mrs. Woolsey 35 S. Grand Ave Osborn Ohio, 8
    - Verso: Mrs. Woolsey 35 S. Grand Ave Osborn Ohio, 8-verso
    - Caption: "Pan American Flight" Off Porto Bello En Route From France Field to Columbia[Colombia], 9
    - San Francisco has radiator [illegible] off Colombia or Ecuador, 10
    - Verso: San Francisco has radiator [illegible] off Colombia or Ecuador, 10-verso
    - Use this along Pacific jungle coast of Colombia or Ecuador; Caption: "Detroit" "San Francisco" "St. Louis" passing Purto Bello; R. R. en route to Bogota, Columbia [sic], 11
    - Verso: Use this along Pacific jungle coast of Colombia or Ecuador, 11-verso
    - LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane to be used on the Pan-American Flight shown here with close-up of retractable landing-gear, 12
    - Verso: LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane to be used on the Pan-American Flight shown here with close-up of retractable landing-gear, 12-verso
    - Cotopaxi, most active volcano in Ecuador, 13
    - Verso: Cotopaxi, most active volcano in Ecuador, 13-verso
    - Cotopaxi Vol., Ecuador, 14
    - Verso: Cotopaxi Vol., Ecuador, 14-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight plane landing in water], 15
    - [Two pilots sitting in a Pan-American Flight plane labled "Major H.A. Dargue L.T. E.C. Whitehead"], 16
    - Embajada; Return to Mrs. Benton, 17
    - Verso: Embajada; Return to Mrs. Benton, 17-verso
    - The Loening amphibian, 18
    - Verso: The Loening amphibian, 18-verso
    - [Pan-American pilot standing in front of his plane labled "Capt. L.C. Eaker L.T. MS Fairchild"], 19
    - Montevideo, 20
    - Verso: Montevideo, 20-verso
    - [Two Pan-American pilots in their plane labled "Major H.A. Dargue L.T. E.C. Whitehead"], 21
    - Garden in San Pedro - near San Jose - Costa Rica, 22
    - Verso: Garden in San Pedro - near San Jose - Costa Rica, 22-verso
    - [Caption: Off Ponto Bello en route from France Field to Columbia], 23
    - [Three Pan-American Flight planes over water and mountains], 24
    - Over to Caribbean, 25
    - Verso: Over to Caribbean, 25-verso
    - [Three Pan-American Flight planes flying over water], 26
    - Miller Field during training period, 27
    - Verso: Miller Field during training period, 27-verso
    - Mt. Chimborago [Chimborazo], Ecuador. The colossus of the Andes, 28
    - Verso: Mt. Chimborago [Chimborazo], Ecuador. The colossus of the Andes, 28-verso
    - Havana[?], 29
    - Verso: Havana[?], 29-verso
    - Ambassador Crowder, center in white, (Havana) gave a reception to the P.A.F., 30
    - Verso: Ambassador Crowder, center in white, (Havana) gave a reception to the P.A.F., 30-verso
    - Verso: In the Aycentamiento[?] (Mayor's office) Santiago, Cuba, 31
    - In the Aycentamiento[?] (Mayor's office) Santiago, Cuba, 31-verso
    - President Borno (in center with glasses) saw us off from Haiti., 32
    - Verso: President Borno (in center with glasses) saw us off from Haiti., 32-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight plane], 33
    - [U.S. Army Pan-American Flight logo], 34
    - [Pan-American Flight planes lined up in the water] Caption: Paita - Peru, 35
    - [Pan-American Flight plane], 36
    - San Millan, near Puerto Cabello, Venezuela, 37
    - Verso: San Millan, near Puerto Cabello, Venezuela, 37-verso
    - A railroad in Venezuela, 38
    - Verso: A railroad in Venezuela, 38-verso
    - [The U.S Army Pan-American Fliers], 39
    - [Map of the plane routes from the U.S. Army Pan-American Flight], 40